{
    "id": "62d55a9afb724161993d8f3ec1bf72f9",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The consequence of his carelessness was ………………………… he failed.",
            "description": "That can indicate the effect.",
            "answers": [
                "such that",
                "that",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. I am successful does not necessarily make me happy.",
            "description": "That clauses do not normally stand alone as subjects. We use the expression ‘the fact that’ instead of ‘that’.",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "The fact that",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I shall stay is doubtful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How long",
                "How long for",
                "What long"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The news ………………………….. the captain was killed spread like wild fire.",
            "description": "A noun clause can be used in apposition to a noun. In most cases, this is introduced by that.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "of",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He sold the horse …………………………… belonged to his brother.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses that and which can both refer to things or animals.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have no pen …………………………… I can lend.",
            "description": "That is common after words like no, none, nothing etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A man …………………………. is dead needs no comforts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The camel …………………………… was bought from Arabia is very big.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses both which and that can refer to animals and things. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I found the key …………………………. I had lost.",
            "description": "We use which to refer to things. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You can eat as much …………………………… you want.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "what",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The master was annoyed …………………………. his servant had not carried out his orders.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "that",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. there is life, there is hope.",
            "description": "As long as is used to indicate a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "As long as",
                "As soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}